Excuse me, sir. Question for you.
Yeah.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I'm not a millionaire.
Yeah?
I wish I were.
I'm a lawyer. I used to be a
millionaire, but my ex-wife has most of the money.
I got one quick minute with you real quick.
Real quick.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
Six million.
Six, seven million.
That's for yourself or the business?
No, the business is myself.
I own like 20 companies still.
$50 million.
I was doing about eight million a year.
$17 and a half million.
$17 and a half million?
You've got a big election coming up.
Who are you voting for in this election?
I'll give you one guess.
Because we're asking millionaires who they're
voting for just to get perspectives.
I live in a split household.
I'm going to leave it at that.
Who are you pulling towards though?
We have four daughters.
I vote for the party.
I don't vote for the individual.
So you like the party?
Yeah.
Democrat or Republican?
Today, we are in one of the
wealthiest cities in the entire United States
to go around asking millionaires
and billionaires how they became wealthy
and who they're going to be
voting for in the 2024 presidential election
between Donald Trump and Kamala Harris.
We're in
Austin, Texas, home to nearly
40,000 millionaires and over 10 billionaires.
And we're going to be figuring
out their secrets to becoming financially free
and who they're going to be casting
their vote for to run the country
for the next four years.
So with that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
Excuse me, sir.
Quick question for you. Go ahead.
Have you ever been broke before?
No. No?
In what line of business? I'm a very wealthy dude.
Yeah? Yeah.
What line of business did you end up in?
I was.
I was a builder developer.
So you were in real estate.
Real estate. Buy dirt.
My father always told me, buy dirt.
Any kind of dirt you can buy.
Do you like commercial or residential?
I do both. Yeah. Did both.
What was the best real estate transaction you ever had?
The best real estate deal you ever did?
Take a look at that.
Right there. Best transaction.
Most expensive transaction, but my best.
So give me one though.
Tell me about one deal that
you closed that you're really proud about.
Well, I named a lot of
streets after a lot of people.
The thing I'm most proud of
is naming my streets after my
kids.
Right.
So that's forever.
Yeah. Where are you from?
As far as New York City.
New York City?
Yeah.
Are you a billionaire?
No.
No? Close though.
Maybe.
Yeah. Well, real quick.
Couple quick last ones real quick.
So I started a channel here in Austin.
I go all over the country
interviewing the most successful business owners.
Yes.
What was your secret to creating wealth in real estate?
Failure.
Yes. You got to fail
before you get hungry to make.
Yeah.
If you don't fail and you just
keep, you know, and just roll and whatever,
you're not the hungry. You got to be hungry.
How did you find properties to close on and build?
Like, how did you find deals?
It's very hard for you kids nowadays.
It was much easier.
It used to be you can buy stuff subject to,
and then it would gain wealth
before you even closed on it.
Yeah.
That was the key.
No more.
Now it's a risk.
Yeah.
You know?
But stay with it and you'll be successful.
What's your best negotiation advice for anybody in business?
You're at the table with a heavy hitter.
How did you close all these deals?
What was your best negotiation advice?
Don't impulse it.
Let them make it like you don't really want it.
Or need it.
You can't be desperate to get a deal done.
No.
Can't be desperate.
Yeah.
And you got to use your own money.
Don't use the banks because they are
the only ones that make the money.
Yeah.
So what's the lesson about money
that banks don't want people to know?
Don't always listen to what they say.
If they say they want 6%,
you make it that it's 4%.
Otherwise you're not doing it.
Then you start walking out.
Oh, excuse me.
No, no, no.
Come back.
Come back to the table.
Never settle on your first offer.
I love that.
All right.
In terms of revenue, what was the most
amount of money you made in a single year?
At your business revenue?
6 million.
6, 7 million.
That's for yourself or the business?
No, the business is myself.
I own like 20 companies still.
Actually.
Thank you, my friend.
And who are you voting
for next week in the election?
Trump.
Why Trump?
He's a dick, first of all.
He really is.
He's a pompous ass.
But he gets it done.
He's a businessman like me.
Yeah.
And he's crude, rude.
Thank you, my friend.
I appreciate you, man.
Have a great day.
You guys be good.
So we just got our first interview out here.
A wealthy real estate developer from New York
City who just gave you guys the blueprint
on how to negotiate.
He said no impulses.
You got to be willing to walk away
from the deal because the most desperate person has
no leverage in a negotiation.
And he said he's going to be
voting for Trump in this election next week.
But we got to go find some more
millionaires and figure out who they're voting for.
Let's go see what they have to say.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I'm not a millionaire.
Yeah?
I wish I were.
What line of business are you in?
I'm a lawyer.
I used to be a millionaire.
My ex-wife has most of the money.
Actually.
So what did you learn from that divorce?
Don't get divorced because in every
state, the woman gets all the money.
How much money did you lose from your divorce?
Several million dollars.
What are you doing to
kind of bounce back from that?
And I ask because I started a channel.
I grew it to a couple million followers
where I asked successful people some advice to the
younger generation and how they built
their wealth and how they became successful.
So just wanted to ask
you a couple of quick questions.
I'm a lawyer and I went out.
I worked in big law.
I made a lot of money in the dot-com era.
The ex-wife has all of it.
She has all of that money right now.
She kept all the house and she
lives very high on the hog in Florida.
I got remarried and I'm now separated and
decided not to get divorced even though we're
separated because I don't want
her to have all my retirement.
So it's safe to say marriage is a business.
Marriage is an important economic decision and
you should be very careful about that.
Particularly if you are the man or the
money earner and the woman doesn't work, which is
both of my wife fell into that category.
Yeah.
And if you are building wealth,
you certainly have a prenuptial agreement.
And even though you want to
marry for love, just be careful.
What was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
It was paper money and I eventually lost
it because I didn't convert it to real money
soon enough.
How much was that though?
$17.5 million.
$17.5 million?
Yeah.
What happened that you made $17 million?
That's incredible.
It was stock options in companies with IPOs
in 1999 and 2000, the height of the dot-com
era.
The bubble, as they say.
My shares were locked up because after
the IPO, insiders have to wait six months.
Six months was the middle of the crash.
And by the time I convinced my Merrill
Lynch broker to sell the shares, they had collapsed
and it was worth $750,000 and
he finally sold them for $350,000.
So sell too soon.
You never lose money selling too soon.
You got amazing advice, sir.
Real quick.
You've got a big election coming up.
Who are you voting for in this election?
I don't talk politics in public
just because it's so divisive now.
Who do you think is going to win?
Personally, I hope that Kamala Harris does not
win for the same reason I did not want
Hillary Clinton to be president.
I don't think either of them are qualified.
Did you know that for the first time ever
in history, you can legally bet on the election?
I did know that.
Yeah.
There's a platform called CalSheet where
people can bet on who's winning.
Right now, it's closer to like 50-50, so you
can make some pretty good returns if you bet
on using this platform called CalSheet.
Yeah.
I mean, look, there's only 1% or 2% at issue.
We need to go, but there's
only 1% or 2% at issue.
It's going to be really close.
Who knows?
It depends upon how they count the ballots.
Guys, you hear it time and time again.
The most important decision that you will ever
make is the person you decide to marry.
And like I said at the end of that
interview, guys, for the first time in history, you can
legally bet on who you think will win
the 2024 presidential election thanks to a platform
called CalSheet.
CalSheet makes it possible for you to bet on not just who you think
will win the general election, but the people who will win the presidential election.
will win the general election, but the people who will win the general election.
But who you think is going to win the
individual swing states in places like Georgia or Arizona.
Who you think is going to take
control of the House or the Senate.
And you can bet on way
more than just politics in the election.
This platform, CalSheet, has already facilitated
a billion dollars worth of trades.
And if you're at all invested in politics
in the general election, and you have confidence
behind which candidate you think you will win,
waste no more time and head over to calsheet.com
slash hard knocks to place your bet on who
you think is going to win the general election.
And if you use all of the options you
have, you are going to win the general election.
Go to our link at calsheet.com slash
hard knocks and deposit a hundred dollars.
You will receive a $20 credit to place your bet.
And the beautiful thing is, is both candidates
are trading about 50 50 meaning no matter
which candidate you place a bet on, you
can have some serious returns on your investment.
So head over to calsheet.com using the
link down in the description or calsheet.com slash
hard knocks, but with that being
said, let's go get this next interview.
Excuse me, sir.
What question for you?
I know who you are.
I see you online all the time.
Yeah, it's not that I know you.
You're just not here.
Could I interview you real quick for the channel?
How many followers do you have?
Just so he knows. He doesn't know who you are.
9.1 million across social media.
That's pretty good.
Yeah? Shoot.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
See, I'm 47 now.
I was a millionaire once before when I was 27.
Lost everything.
Filed bankruptcy when I was 31.
Took me about 10 years to build back up.
Did you come from a lot of money?
No.
No?
So what was that first
business you started that went bankrupt?
An excavation company.
Excavation?
Yeah.
I was 24 years old.
By the time I was 28, 29,
I was doing about $8 million a year.
Actually.
31, 2008, crisis happened.
Lost everything.
Had to file bankruptcy.
Took two years off.
Met my beautiful wife.
Traveled the country and started over again.
So what's the greatest lesson
that you've learned about entrepreneurship?
Building numerous companies to multi-million dollars.
You lost it all at one point.
Made it all back.
What's the greatest lesson you've
learned about entrepreneurship throughout your career?
That you can tell people more about you.
About what not to do than what they can do.
Yeah.
And find a good wife to support
you through the million businesses that you'll start.
The other thing is it just takes a
whole lot more effort than what people realize.
Because nobody else is going to do it for you.
You have to do it yourself.
There's nobody else.
There's no owner.
There's no VP.
You're the owner.
You're the VP.
You have to make it happen.
So in other words, nobody's coming to save you.
Nobody's coming to save you.
Yeah.
How did you get the money to start your business?
Sweat equity.
Yeah.
You worked your ass off.
I went to school at night to learn
how to basically be a project manager, owner.
I learned how to run
the equipment at the trade school.
So I worked the job of the day running equipment.
And at night, I went to school to learn how
to be a project manager, estimator, negotiate contracts, all that stuff.
So I was hustling.
But you ended up in excavation.
Yeah.
There's a saying, riches are in the niches.
You know what you're talking about.
I'm pretty impressed.
Did you almost kind of create your own market there?
I'm just curious why excavation out of all
the – why that niche particularly out of
any business you could have been in?
For me personally, I love being outside.
I love building something.
And I hate – that was
the only kind of construction I liked.
I tried every other trade.
I love moving the earth.
I love taking like a place
like this and building into something new.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
And, you know, we're doing a video
where we're asking millionaires who they're voting for.
We got a big election coming up next week.
Who are you voting for next week?
I'll give you one guess.
You're voting for Trump.
Donald J. Trump.
All day.
Every day.
Do you think he's going to win?
I do.
I think it's going to be a landslide.
Yeah.
And what's the number one
reason why you're voting for Trump?
I'm curious.
First of all, he loves his country.
And there's a lot of people in
this country that don't love this country.
Yeah.
He loves what it stands for.
He loves the foundation.
He loves the Constitution.
He loves freedom.
He loves liberty.
And he loves the pursuit of happiness.
Yeah.
Thank you so much for your time, Scott.
You bet, man.
You got an amazing advice.
You bet.
We just got another multimillionaire out here.
And he took his business to nearly
$10 million before the time he was 30.
But he went bankrupt.
He lost it all.
And it just goes to show, guys, that the
realest entrepreneurs in the game, you can take everything
away from them, their businesses, their money, everything.
But you can't take away the skill sets
and the mindsets that they developed to build
million-dollar businesses.
Great interview out here.
And we got another business mogul that
said he's going to be voting for Trump.
And this is crazy surprising
because we're in Austin right now.
This is the most liberal city in Texas.
The last couple of decades, it's gone
blue for presidential candidates and other people
running for office out here.
But it's 3-0 Trump so far.
We're going to win.
We got to go get another one and see
who these people out here are going to be voting
for.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
I started a channel here in Austin at UT.
I grew it to 9 million followers.
A what?
I started a channel at the University of Texas.
I grew it to 9 million followers.
Real quick.
I go all over asking successful people two
or three quick questions on their best advice
to the younger generation.
Can I get one quick minute with you real quick?
Real quick.
OK.
What line of business are you in?
I'm retired.
What did you do?
I was in finance.
Did you ever own a
business at any point in time?
Yes, I did.
What company?
What type of company?
I own a couple of restaurants.
A couple of restaurants?
I did.
What type of restaurants?
American Fair.
Yeah?
What was the name of it?
Bogies Grill in Taproom.
How many locations did you have?
Three.
There's tough margins in the restaurant business, right?
Right?
You're either hugely successful or you go out of business.
That's why banks don't lend money to restaurants.
It's all privately financed.
So what were you doing in the finance business?
I was a bond trader.
In terms of revenue, right?
Maybe either on Wall Street or when you
were in the restaurant business, what was the most
amount of money that you made in a single year?
I'm not sure.
I'm not going to share that with you.
Just revenue, not personal income.
Oh, revenue?
$50 million.
$50 million?
Yes.
You were in the money business.
What's a lesson about money that
banks don't want people to know?
Give me some game right here, something that
they won't learn in school right here, because
I know that you have some insight and knowledge.
You know what?
Listen, I'm going to just tell you.
What you're going to learn in
school is really, really important, okay?
What you learn in business, you learn
hands-on, and you got to learn it yourself.
And the best advice I can give a trader
or people who get into trading, if any great
trader tells you he never lost
money, then he's lying to you.
Yeah.
So there's a lot of loss that comes with it.
Of course.
That's how you learn.
Right.
What separates the middle class from wealthy people
in today's world in terms of how they
perceive or look at money?
So the middle class saves, the upper class invests.
Into what?
Whatever.
What do you think is the best industry people
should be looking to get into to make their
money work for them?
You know what?
My philosophy is you invest by walking around.
So it's kind of like the Peter Lynch model.
So if you walk up this street right here,
and I live in a house with five women, and
everyone in my house has an Apple product.
Everyone in my house wears Lulu.
Everyone in my house wears Lulu Lemon.
You know, so on and so forth.
You don't have to, it's
not any, it's not rocket science.
Thank you, my friend.
I really appreciate you.
Good luck with everything.
And real quick, who are you voting for?
Because we're asking millionaires who they're
voting for just to get perspectives.
I live in a split household.
I'm going to leave it at that.
Who are you pulling towards though?
We have four daughters.
Yeah.
Well, who are you pulling towards though?
I vote for the party.
I don't vote for the individual.
You like the party?
Yeah.
Democrat or Republican?
Republican.
You're Republican, so you're going for Trump.
Do you think he's going to win or?
I don't know.
Yeah.
Okay, good.
Have a great day.
Look, you guys, we just got a feel for
who the millionaires at who are going to be voting
for in the general election, but
that's a wrap on today's video.
So be sure to leave a like and
subscribe for amazing content we've got coming very, very
soon because every week we're asking the wealthiest
Americans, the top 1%, how they became financially
free and how you can do the exact same thing.
And if you haven't joined yet, I have
a private entrepreneur community called the School of
Mentors.
We're inside of it every single week.
I host live calls with the millionaires
and the billionaires that I interview on this
channel.
I have a website where you can learn
directly from them and ask questions about how they
became successful and learn skills like how to
sell, how to market, how to create wealth
and real estate and a bunch of other different industries.
You do not want to miss
out on this opportunity at all.
So to join my community, use the link down
in the description of this video or use the
link that's up here on the screen right now.
I can't wait to see
on the inside of the community.
With that being said, we'll
see you in the next video.